export const emojiCards = [
  { question: "🚫 + 🧸", answer: "Noted." },
  { question: "🍞 + 👁️ + 🎵", answer: "Lofi music." },
  { question: "🥤 + 🎂", answer: "Cupcake." },
  { question: "🍯 + 🐝", answer: "Honey Bee." },
  { question: "🐮 + 👦🏼", answer: "Cowboy." },
  { question: "👩🏼‍🍳 + 💋", answer: "Chef's Kiss." },
  { question: "🧠 + 📦", answer: "Memory Box." },
  { question: "🎈 + 🌽", answer: "Popcorn." },
  { question: "🤪 + 🦆", answer: "Silly duck." },
  { question: "🥷 + 🐢", answer: "Ninja Turtle." },
]
